[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 19, "question": "What's your overview?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "overview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 20, "answer": "It's a big night for Mitt Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "big", "night", "for", "Mitt", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "So how significant is Romney's position right now?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "significant", "is", "Romney", "'s", "position", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Well, look.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "What went wrong with Gingrich this week, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "went", "wrong", "with", "Gingrich", "this", "week", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Well, it's interesting because I don't think Newt Gingrich could decide who he was or what he was.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "Newt", "Gingrich", "could", "decide", "who", "he", "was", "or", "what", "he", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Buffalo"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "Wolf?", "question_tokens": ["Wolf", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "I'm a Buffalo Bills fan.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "Buffalo", "Bills", "fan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Gloria?", "question_tokens": ["Gloria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "All right.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "All right?", "question_tokens": ["All", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "And John, I know your allegiance.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "John", ",", "I", "know", "your", "allegiance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Are you surprised that he's now beginning to beat his chest a bit?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "surprised", "that", "he", "'s", "now", "beginning", "to", "beat", "his", "chest", "a", "bit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "I'm not surprised at all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "surprised", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "He's going to throw the kitchen sink at him, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "going", "to", "throw", "the", "kitchen", "sink", "at", "him", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Well, it sure looks like it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "sure", "looks", "like", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Are you going to stop baring your teeth in more places?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "stop", "baring", "your", "teeth", "in", "more", "places", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Now, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Have you had a word with him?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "a", "word", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "I thought it was fantastic.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "it", "was", "fantastic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "What is the big challenge for Mitt Romney, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "big", "challenge", "for", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "I think for Mitt it's just to continue to put himself out there, continue to show that he's got a plan to get America moving forward.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "for", "Mitt", "it", "'s", "just", "to", "continue", "to", "put", "himself", "out", "there", ",", "continue", "to", "show", "that", "he", "'s", "got", "a", "plan", "to", "get", "America", "moving", "forward", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "On a human level, how do you as his daughters feel about the bombardment that's coming his way?", "question_tokens": ["On", "a", "human", "level", ",", "how", "do", "you", "as", "his", "daughters", "feel", "about", "the", "bombardment", "that", "'s", "coming", "his", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Well, it's never actually fun to experience that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "never", "actually", "fun", "to", "experience", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "CC", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Does that help the Republican Party?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "help", "the", "Republican", "Party", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "USHMAN: I think part of the process of the primary is to go through this and to go through all the different things you'll see in the general election.", "answer_tokens": ["USHMAN", ":", "I", "think", "part", "of", "the", "process", "of", "the", "primary", "is", "to", "go", "through", "this", "and", "to", "go", "through", "all", "the", "different", "things", "you", "'ll", "see", "in", "the", "general", "election", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "I mean little bit graceless, wouldn't you think?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "little", "bit", "graceless", ",", "would", "n't", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "I'm not really sure I'd say that as graceless.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "really", "sure", "I", "'d", "say", "that", "as", "graceless", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Governor, why do you think Mitt Romney has such a thumping victory tonight?", "question_tokens": ["Governor", ",", "why", "do", "you", "think", "Mitt", "Romney", "has", "such", "a", "thumping", "victory", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "It was a big night for Florida.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "big", "night", "for", "Florida", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Suddenly this huge turnaround and it seems to be based around Mitt Romney's better performances in the debates and this relentless negativity of the campaign, which I'll come to in a moment, but why Mitt Romney -- why is he being seen as the savior economically, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Suddenly", "this", "huge", "turnaround", "and", "it", "seems", "to", "be", "based", "around", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", "better", "performances", "in", "the", "debates", "and", "this", "relentless", "negativity", "of", "the", "campaign", ",", "which", "I", "'ll", "come", "to", "in", "a", "moment", ",", "but", "why", "Mitt", "Romney", "--", "why", "is", "he", "being", "seen", "as", "the", "savior", "economically", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "COTT: I think -- I think what Floridians looked at is they look at he's a business guy.", "answer_tokens": ["COTT", ":", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "what", "Floridians", "looked", "at", "is", "they", "look", "at", "he", "'s", "a", "business", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "Wouldn't it be better for the party to have at least some positivity creeping in here?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "it", "be", "better", "for", "the", "party", "to", "have", "at", "least", "some", "positivity", "creeping", "in", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "You know I think when people go to the polls, here's what they say.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "I", "think", "when", "people", "go", "to", "the", "polls", ",", "here", "'s", "what", "they", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "I mean, if Floridians believe that the president is actually turning around the situation, that's good for him, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "if", "Floridians", "believe", "that", "the", "president", "is", "actually", "turning", "around", "the", "situation", ",", "that", "'s", "good", "for", "him", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNPS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Are you prepared to back Mr. Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "prepared", "to", "back", "Mr.", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "I'm going to -- I'm going to support the Republican nominee.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "--", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "support", "the", "Republican", "nominee", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rubio"], "LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "He really needs a bit of more this, I think, and momentum will take him to nomination, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["He", "really", "needs", "a", "bit", "of", "more", "this", ",", "I", "think", ",", "and", "momentum", "will", "take", "him", "to", "nomination", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Well, I mean, you know, a lot of wags are saying -- Senator Rubio said that if he wins Florida he wins the nomination.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "know", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "wags", "are", "saying", "--", "Senator", "Rubio", "said", "that", "if", "he", "wins", "Florida", "he", "wins", "the", "nomination", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Catherine"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "I think the big question for a lot of the GOP and Republican establishment so to speak is, can Newt still do damage to Mitt Romney even if Mitt Romney gets the nomination?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "big", "question", "for", "a", "lot", "of", "the", "GOP", "and", "Republican", "establishment", "so", "to", "speak", "is", ",", "can", "Newt", "still", "do", "damage", "to", "Mitt", "Romney", "even", "if", "Mitt", "Romney", "gets", "the", "nomination", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", ",", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "ORGAN: Look, Catherine, let me ask you.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Look", ",", "Catherine", ",", "let", "me", "ask", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GOP"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Isn't it -- you know, aren't we in the position here where the longer this goes on, it's better for Mitt Romney if he's the one that wins to have this bruising encounter with Gingrich on months on end?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "--", "you", "know", ",", "are", "n't", "we", "in", "the", "position", "here", "where", "the", "longer", "this", "goes", "on", ",", "it", "'s", "better", "for", "Mitt", "Romney", "if", "he", "'s", "the", "one", "that", "wins", "to", "have", "this", "bruising", "encounter", "with", "Gingrich", "on", "months", "on", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "Well, I think there could be a fine line.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "could", "be", "a", "fine", "line", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "The phenomenal Tea Party bursting on to scene and then disappearing almost as fast?", "question_tokens": ["The", "phenomenal", "Tea", "Party", "bursting", "on", "to", "scene", "and", "then", "disappearing", "almost", "as", "fast", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Well, it hasn't disappeared whatsoever.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "has", "n't", "disappeared", "whatsoever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "You know what do you think of the other two candidates?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "other", "two", "candidates", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Well, some watchers, you know, they're speculating that perhaps Rick Santorum is staying in in the hopes of being VP on a Romney ticket.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "some", "watchers", ",", "you", "know", ",", "they", "'re", "speculating", "that", "perhaps", "Rick", "Santorum", "is", "staying", "in", "in", "the", "hopes", "of", "being", "VP", "on", "a", "Romney", "ticket", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "I wouldn't rule out Newt Gingrich making yet another comeback, would you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "rule", "out", "Newt", "Gingrich", "making", "yet", "another", "comeback", ",", "would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "But Newt -- I've been covering Newt Gingrich since the late '80s.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "Newt", "--", "I", "'ve", "been", "covering", "Newt", "Gingrich", "since", "the", "late", "'80s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "If the economy continues to improve right up to November, he's going to hit a homerun, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["If", "the", "economy", "continues", "to", "improve", "right", "up", "to", "November", ",", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "hit", "a", "homerun", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "Well, that's a big if.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "big", "if", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "RP", "TO", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Would you -- would you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "--", "would", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "I think it all boils down to electability, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "all", "boils", "down", "to", "electability", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "Has Mitt Romney now made that sort of tipping point move, do you think, to where he's a genuine frontrunner?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "Mitt", "Romney", "now", "made", "that", "sort", "of", "tipping", "point", "move", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "to", "where", "he", "'s", "a", "genuine", "frontrunner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Who, if you're -- if you're Obama, who do you least want to take on?", "question_tokens": ["Who", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "--", "if", "you", "'re", "Obama", ",", "who", "do", "you", "least", "want", "to", "take", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Probably Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul"], "LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Santorum and Paul, where are they in this?", "question_tokens": ["Santorum", "and", "Paul", ",", "where", "are", "they", "in", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "Well, I mean, Paul wasn't really competing in Florida.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "Paul", "was", "n't", "really", "competing", "in", "Florida", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "Does it make him -- no, but does it make him a valuable tool to whoever wants to be the nominee?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "make", "him", "--", "no", ",", "but", "does", "it", "make", "him", "a", "valuable", "tool", "to", "whoever", "wants", "to", "be", "the", "nominee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ":", "DT", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "Well, if he has -- if he has a lot of delegates in the end and if he has a lot of public support, I mean, the nominee is going to want every single former opponent, you know, to line up behind him.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "he", "has", "--", "if", "he", "has", "a", "lot", "of", "delegates", "in", "the", "end", "and", "if", "he", "has", "a", "lot", "of", "public", "support", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "the", "nominee", "is", "going", "to", "want", "every", "single", "former", "opponent", ",", "you", "know", ",", "to", "line", "up", "behind", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "Santorum?", "question_tokens": ["Santorum", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Santorum I think tries to stay in it for awhile because there's clearly this bloc of voters who don't want Romney, who are more conservative.", "answer_tokens": ["Santorum", "I", "think", "tries", "to", "stay", "in", "it", "for", "awhile", "because", "there", "'s", "clearly", "this", "bloc", "of", "voters", "who", "do", "n't", "want", "Romney", ",", "who", "are", "more", "conservative", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christina Aguilera"]}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 711, "question": "Barack Obama or Mitt Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Barack", "Obama", "or", "Mitt", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 712, "answer": "Suddenly I feel like I'm Christina Aguilera on the \"Voice\" or something.", "answer_tokens": ["Suddenly", "I", "feel", "like", "I", "'m", "Christina", "Aguilera", "on", "the", "``", "Voice", "''", "or", "something", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "Why would anybody in the modern age really want to be the president given the unbearable workload, stress, the attention?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "anybody", "in", "the", "modern", "age", "really", "want", "to", "be", "the", "president", "given", "the", "unbearable", "workload", ",", "stress", ",", "the", "attention", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "I mean, yes, we're talking about -- I can't imagine, it is, you know, we should say this from time to time because we all spend so much time tearing apart the candidates and, you know, in being justly critical of them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "yes", ",", "we", "'re", "talking", "about", "--", "I", "ca", "n't", "imagine", ",", "it", "is", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "should", "say", "this", "from", "time", "to", "time", "because", "we", "all", "spend", "so", "much", "time", "tearing", "apart", "the", "candidates", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "in", "being", "justly", "critical", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 754, "question": "But actually you've got -- as you say, you've got to really want this, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "actually", "you", "'ve", "got", "--", "as", "you", "say", ",", "you", "'ve", "got", "to", "really", "want", "this", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 755, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]